Okay, Wack Morning Herald
[Applause]
[Music] Checking
the walls repeatedly,
the HCD,
we're done, and then
I sign books. Are there any here?
Then 30
looks like a book of hate. Never
enter work next Thursday.
It's a Vietnamese one. Have you had
your first picture? Why is this
picture on the first page of the book of
100 watts?
[Music]
3 dollars. Why is this picture on that? That
's the name of the penance. Choose your
yesterday in the beautiful place. Make a nice place because
we're going to study relation. More mean
songs. Make your mind more beautiful. You
can make highlights of the spade young. Not
this picture chosen. That's mine. That's
your mind. It's especially the
water. Little thoughts that go through the
mind, but the mind is very
beautiful.
For this reason we are here. That's that
page. Make the next
picture.
Yeah, okay,
you know a lot of money with it. I have my
camera to sell, but the goal of the
camera is to make pictures of later.
Okay, I have then when the appointment
is, and the second meaning is  If
the consumer doesn't make more money than you
do, a chamber choir is a strange
credit card, it's okay. We can have a good car, have a
house, and also
quality stones, and there's music. The way
then came to use it,
and everything just for yourself. You
need
this credit card less and less and less and
less. The opinions at Tesla,
Tesla Model S car, you buy the
user, friend of the, and bring him to
help,
line from here to there,
yuan, you are
generating more together than that she has used,
consumed, because and enjoyed, have a
core, can earth and also
have a Tesla, but differently, because there is, okay to do, have that it's okay to
have good things, there is the dad, uses the
good cause,
the new world, money, you can't already,
I hated, know no lack of,
I have him together, in this picture, the more Merkel's
American jazz band,
Moratti, you don't exactly spend more money
than she earned, took
photos with it because she came less,
I, seeds, than before
[Music],
if you can do more good things, it's too
narrow with that.  It's about talking to other people on
Monday,
June in Bern. It's about your
friends and family's interest. When
you think about it, when you get money
to buy things for the family,
YouTube gentlemen are business class.
Business class is used so that we can do
something for poor people today. The demand
to support projects means
you use your money together, and
the best part is that the calculation
could generate an additional bank.
But until it encourages other people,
especially to do things, in
Muslim Germany there is a
good custom. This is one of the five
rules of Muslims: that
every person's income should go to
five or ten aid organizations.
It is expected that every Muslim
should do this. Great things are needed when we
make our friends do this. We have particularly
good own series brands. If I
ask you today for a donation of
100, that means giving to my organization,
but even better, me and I'll
make your own aid organization. The
world's best behind Merkel's non-profit
organization. Even the price is more
powerful, and if you create your
own aid organization here, it's
easy. Make 16 percent.
I am  The tool, the money, to where you give it,
the aid organization,
your mother's name, my husband, nicknamed
my mother, really a
name, issued as well as that, prepared, I
have two great Elisabeths in my
life, or Frankie, but her boyfriend calls
her, her friends have called her banker,
we have an aid organization, the
power, the bank, her position, would have
asked me, what is a banker, I said
that's my mother, knows that, yes,
if you, that's your own help, of which you're
used to by now,
you can then, earthquake victims in
western China, flamenco,
let's get to it completely correctly,
lessons for poor children in Japan, is more
powerful, that's also meant that way, there are
also men who, the picture,
it has a very deep meaning,
I believe it, a 100 dollar, 100, great
picture,
two parts,
I don't know if anyone
can guess, a brave one, better
two parts,
[Music]
for, with the ball,
the lists, chamber
president, food, I came, I say, say, no more, there is,
because
I, in my pocket, later, do, very
good answer, came, Anna Schiller  The camera,
Schiller Potter film, is experimenting.
He no longer explains the diamond.
No one said there are
two types of people. A
first type of user uses their funny
burn. Can I, along with
people, the PC world. Person in the picture
burns. I can see myself in his online
as the right side of the burning man.
She burns her karma. She is queen
kings. In the basket is drinking coffee or something.
Western direction and more understandable.
They are all missing people. The other person
recognizes consumers of seeds.
Produces his person on the right
side. Needs seeds on right. The
person on the right side sometimes looks like this.
It is one of the best seeds of the
plants. Can get work. Work has fired the
other people. Right, so
better understands very well how to
relax. Turn on the rock roll music.
Herbalife could drink good coffee.
The attacks from the restaurant. Eat.
Okay,
I will do that this afternoon.
It is important to know how to
relax. Then you also do good
collecting while the fun.
Sit down to have good balance. Be a
company car. The seeds burn.
To drink the good coffee when  I'm
recharged in the batteries,
storing the upper body, half of many people,
so that now the right one
burns, probably collecting, worked too hard
to prepare this event,
intelligent, sometimes I need to take a break,
in the city I need to relax,
rock 'n' roll with 4
days, another part, the thing is,
getting the US auto market is also good
together,
I think that in the children's class, the
donkey and the ticker, 100, what is this
picture about,
we talked about it,
yes, where
it is, there are
three types, the suffering, be the
last, people have to become and die
and nobody cares, they have it, she
is not beautiful,
next to USB, if only, was maybe once
already in the past, now she is
no longer,
it is not rich,
that is not young,
a flamenco, no longer flamenco dancing,
the numbers, motto not, now
nobody wants to look at her anymore, until you have it, and
that happens to old people in New Orleans,
means that this happens, all of this will
come to a time when we are old and alone,
nobody wants to spend time,
that's no fun playing with other people
anymore,
okay.  This is a perceived before,
this is the future for all of us.
I have, this is a little difficult.
The Mexicans should know it.
We talked about this in Mexico.
Here with you,
she had the idea.
[Music] They
should work hard to
practice later and not stop before
we change on the eighth flight on the eighth floor
or others. If we do that,
then we start under. We should go to those
floors to
see the teacher directly. They don't go out too early, also
live, but until the 9th.
If you don't, if you didn't reach the teacher,
the meditation, then you have
n't meditated.
Show me the eight floors. No matter how they
did it now,
it's just a warm-up exercise. Okay, it's
not a real meditation. A
lovely medal for that. Set your
next picture, which is very simple.
[Music]
Good morning, I'm from txtr politics.
It means to them to touch.
Use that as a
fad. Do
n't make yourself famous, and something in
that direction, then you
really understand. And associations are such an upgrade
to the 1.
That's the device and balls
that.  Mantra means I want to act,
I want to talk, we
or I want to think like a brother. There's
nothing in my teacher that does
n't come from me, and my teacher is
like a diamond in the super
[Applause]
dollar [
Applause] don't forget
that he holds them
[Music]
because to the absolute
[Applause]
all cell phones should go Stanley
investment ok last ok know the
six I am that need explanation the
eggplant you have vegetables in the USA that are
n't dazzling eggplant that exists here
yes is very cheap the same Merkel
has
and yes more and more Marco I him really
not at all that help were
recently with partner Lea Finn Jan they
friends so before the asked there is
a good restaurant sister
also told me a good restaurant to
read stories about good restaurants she
also lives in Paris my partner said
I'll order for you what what do
I get then have they said these things
asked what is this
these offer themselves so different
I said I said it's not
whether there is him not another
name for  The thing I don't
understand is that this appeared. Okay, I
want to, but I see that works. The
helmet is allowed. Park in another
package. In another package,
GMX gives 100 dollars.
He lets it. Now we're doing a
new level.
We're doing it for an hour now in the state parliament. I understand that.
I understand that I'm in the cycle of
rebirth. However, it's not
everything. Not everything is a place to dance.
Sometimes something happens. Good coffee
tastes good to me, and I could have him.
We feed him coffee.
Coffee is also suffering. The television
is the lamb's answer. Because gladly,
some of this class are. Some of these
things are simply sacred. There's grass out there
because we can't do much about it.
Jasmin never lets me
out.
That doesn't really mean much. The
grass. That's not learning. That I give all the
things that look like the possibility.
That's even the things that
look neutral on YouTube. If you
braked with your hand, Jörg Kiehn,
you look at the end. Then a bubble comes out of it.
Separate the water. In this
class, that feels bad and
feels  Hesse in front of the others,
if you put that under cold water,
then it feels so core,
that's an illusion, Huxley,
actually, is a bad place,
immediately much mini for a few minutes in
philosophy, feels so return, but
that's an illusion of manager
nature and is there when you stop
putting the cold water on it
for a few minutes, a coffee
at Apple, but if you stop now,
NATO, NATO internists, the
actual nature comes back, okay, to the
cooking and the coffee, it can say,
it's second nature of life,
what is that, the learning,
it of change, why do
things change, 7 together, go to the
end,
together, have these active, I did a
lot for my teacher, if him, for
many years, I did a deep one
anyway, the result is the goal,
open, the collecting has opened, is the
coffee, and I see coffee on my
table,
someone brought church cafe, for
one thing, collecting was,
I have so many, 2304 predictions about
coffee, four seconds of coffee to trade,
250 seeds consumed, this consumption,
250 cups of coffee, maybe long, so
approximately are  difficult business
cannabis café chamber business the summer
is coming to an end like a tree has it
maybe I won't have any more coffee
there we have maybe I won't have any
more reason to drink coffee
at the thing here on it when things are
used when needed together on an
experiment
every experience we have music to
we need time something about children
every time we do something against something
consume the old collect and then through it
and then changes the
children become just the music on
nature
is pain sometimes you get a
coffee or someone gives in the massage
and you feel better for ten minutes 15
minutes
the march 1 2 against the body parents
when the massage starts at 9 o'clock in the
massage I find and the massage ends
and you feel better really comfortable
feels cool that is an hour
massage got was in the bank but in the
background is the body an hour
parents yes when but we are not
hours he at the thing that
kills you we is the massage therefore
suffer or not is an hour closer
to cancer is a  An hour closer
to your heart,
it looks like something good, like
a break for today.
I would have come for a massage, but
during the massage,
because he also had an important idea. The
idea was
8:30 PM. I have to talk to Nick quickly, which
means you have no strength,
but the word in a company. Fans of a very
malicious boss of the department. Staffing
was perhaps you experience this
particular suffering of a malicious boss.
President, boss is very dear to me. Okay,
malicious boss comes to you. Five
children,
did a great job. That all day,
time to go home and meet a wife,
but the post, but said there is a
problem. Was they, we have a
special project? It is very unusual,
right, very rare, a special
project. My boss, who was intelligent
when he says you have the theater. Almost
after 5 o'clock, still stay here. The advice then,
but at that time I had my
church preparation. I learned right away. I made
an agreement with him.
I therefore stopped,
but I have to go home at 5 o'clock
because my teacher gives a lecture at 7 o'clock, and
that lasts two hours until I  I
come home, that's our agreement.
Sometimes they tried to threaten me.
445, right, we have a special
project, had to stay here after 5 o'clock,
stay here at 7 o'clock.
That's not our agreement.
Unanimously, so you don't like working
here, right? No, I like working
here. Being thrown out, right? To
expand, doesn't threaten. I go and
dream. You now, okay, go, says
okay, send home. Can say in English,
we play out eventually, then
finally check the rating. Is it
only or not? Okay, I have to get out. Okay, go
home. It's become intelligent.
445, maybe that does it, then calls you
into the office. Rhine-Main, in this company, law,
you are the biggest protest. Without you
[Music]
we are lost.
We don't know what to do without you,
without you, only you. This
special project, legally, is a very special one.
Better if you
go home, everyone will run here.
Okay, I'll stay, I'll stay, there is
Dietrich, he set me up. Okay, we have
no power.
The board is called Paul. The boss has Maria.
Taboos, have to do that, that the boss
says  Another person works in the distance,
then they have power over you, not about
why we're talking about this.
Now goes into a special, a
special party, explained power and
power to explain. You have power,
who has the power, ballaballa,
who is the boss of life, knows the
boss of his life, two famous bosses, there is
doubt and the boss, there are
three. For now, there is a woman, says
I can, this second is chamber, then there is the one
today, there are only
negative emotions.
The book now goes on to plans, which is a long
explanation. The
different negative
emotions that we have will be explained.
He tries to understand the past, pride, and
all the garbage in our money,
children, if we could just clean that up,
only have uniforms, then we have a
nice gesture, but now the mind is
not very much garbage.
The swimmers made the guests
and explained that now, the aid plan, the
farmer now spends a lot of time on it,
and we will now do this
together,
game.
He has something more about suffering, as we have
now seen. This morning, people already went out
to more.
We ask ours earlier, let's go
out,
this is to enjoy the ocean, then one goes
to the  Fears out for 15 minutes, then you
get sunburned, then
you change, people say I'd like to go back inside.
You go into a room and that's pleasant,
not too hot, then no
sun,
it's good, had two hours for
this, drilling until you're bored, gladly
fresh air outside in the sun,
it's so nice out here. After
two hours later, then you
have the sun, too hot, I'd like to go back inside.
That's the story of our lives.
Did the pain begin outside? Did it
begin? Is it
when it began? Did it begin? Becoming
unpleasant, first
browser, the moment you got out,
is it? No, no, I want the
first two hours, man, wonderful. The
suffering has grown, has grown,
but they didn't
notice. There's a
very famous story in
American English: The man who
teaches boys goes down a street,
the man hits his head against the
wall.
He will too. Why are you hitting your
head against the wall?
Why are you playing this game? It feels so
good when I stop.
That confirmed yesterday, the sun out
brings that.  Life begins with every note,
but she doesn't notice. Now
bigger and bigger and bigger, and at the
end I said I want to go back in.
Our whole life in suffering that gets bigger
and smaller and bigger,
a smaller one becomes, that's our life. You ca
n't be happy anywhere,
the capacity, you don't even have the
capacity to be happier because I'm
badly together under the power
of two malicious, sharpest old
chambers, and your old negative
emotions, and they are connected to each
other.
Great 630, 26 years old, were five,
six years ago, I was already there, monastery,
only possibly driving my car,
then that would have been very, very big. Lamas came and
said, "
Can you drive the car?" The film is, after all,
driving the car,
because if you drive the Reichstag, don't talk to
him. I said why,
we, yes, one says via the internet, he is a
real one. Yes, one can
bring a dead man, who is from China, 13 eyes, before
four heads, big 10, do
n't talk to him. Then the time
to drive has come, be it two years, there have been
three hours on a
bracket, three big lamas got into the car
because here sits  In the front
passenger seat, but I was sitting so relaxed, they were in the
back. Yes, he's still alive, he
's 95 years old. We had
said to the other great lama,
Michael Ernst, who is learning,
excellently studying,
many in Abidjan, met Abidjan,
Stan is Tim Toupet, what's that, she's
teaching this evening, the great
romantic lama then said, what does that
mean, that I said,
because, and I was lucky because I had
learned exactly that day before,
said that is the second chapter, how
old are you, I should have said,
so Westphalian language, 26, but I
'm afraid,
until 26,
good luck, he has a long life,
in a total, try not to talk,
because in the mountains, one or two
big ones in the back have fallen asleep.
I'm driving, when we drive here in
America, I've
never been to America, then
we say what these things are,
we have come to a change in America,
know, to a cemetery,
Christians, and especially the people who like to be in
the earth, something is, that I said, that
is a cemetery,
that is, yes  Cemetery people die then they
bury them I know what a
waste of space the car is too hot
the public I turn off the
air conditioning
I had chin-length five minutes
that's too cold actually turn off the
air conditioning you have to be too hot do you
think I'm crazy then we chat
and talk for two hours we have a lot of
fun
I will never forget the trip afterwards for
many days I wondered
why he did that with the
air conditioning he isn't
Crazy, but it feels crazy
because the big camp is always trying to teach you
something, which tried to
teach me about the air conditioning. I
came to this point, it taught me that it's
a lab. It would have taught
me that.
You have to observe someone in everyday life. Caution, it
's already finished. They will teach you
something in the car, and
we're driving today, calmly from the left.
I know that's the wrong direction.
Islam said from left to right. Media
view: maybe there's a big
car accident on the right side.
Maybe if I was to the right, it
talks about the air conditioning, even
if you sit somewhere for too long. Then it was
clear to me. In the women's class, for example,
I hope Keller takes a break. Sitting for a
long time, these things are forbidden. Then a
friend says, "Let's
go for a walk on the coast so that it hurts me in the back
because I walk for too long." And the
next one, I would go there now. We sit down there.
That's you. After half an
hour, you go back there again.
That's a problem. That came up, that the
body is a child. You can
make the body impossible. Always wants something
else.
The problem says yes, in this year,
in this system,
we  should be superheroes,
I have that, should be another one
or something like that, just yesterday
the class said that
superhero is bad, the suffering also
burns, good karma is right,
two different ones, I'm sorry if I
lose you, I have
Arsing properly, use the many
superheroes, example photos, party for
these powerful people who don't understand the pen,
okay, as well as the rich people in this
world, Thursday,
who don't understand the pen, I
use it, example, this week when I
design superheroes,
I'm rich people, powerful people, but
they understand, I don't understand the pen, they
burn together, but they can make it, lonely,
these talk, we explain, we
explain how we can use house names to
generate money, to have a good
marriage, the seeds can use, to be
healthy, has that we can
use together, peaceful yesterday,
but if you only made yourself and
you have a good one, every other way,
like you, that she should do that, it's
no fun to be healthy,
you feel bad that you made good money
and the others have no money,
the gods take care of the rest, the
restaurant, you go, you sold money
to me and  Expensive Japanese food,
we did that in changing, but
the task of and no one else can afford
that, imagine
every other one looks through the
window, the trade and they are hungry,
a Josef, yes, you are yourself and is
alone, many people and I have, is
reception, does that make it fun to eat like that,
after the success for you, successful for
yourself, that his pulse feels
lonely,
we want to share that with others, how we
can share that with others, that does, there are
two methods, Matt's
is one method, it is them, that in one of
these teachings is not to
bring Thailand, have accordingly, speak, speak, speak, speak,
it is a method, people, things, to learn, happens, to learn,
that, say,
the second method,
it is simply, successes, were,
earn, a lot of money, have, beautiful
partner, makes, in life, the, 65 years,
have, a, peaceful, yellow, a,
human, billboard, the, beeper,
continent, the, people, come, to you, your, life, you, make, you, have,
earned, so much money, now, you, office, is, that, a,
beautiful, partner, get,
but, quite, healthy, that, is, a,
secret, that, is, a,
living, example, I, that  A successful
trio, a living example, how do
you say that in Spanish, why am
I talking about this, why
somehow this, rather about
superheroes, way I like it, quite, why do
we like the three men, saves the
whole world, has this tomato, unfortunately, knows
who, the format,
transformer, many number-one hits, news,
boats, in a company,
delicacy, and had the three
basic fade understood, that on the
construction, got the say,
called here, he has the blonde, that the
blonde girlfriend came, grasps the
fast car,
but underneath, has saved the whole world,
the most important things, most important
comes first, the girlfriend, strength,
mothball box,
the second is that, also there, is the
third most important, has the whole world,
devices, president stands,
how often has he done that,
why do they make these films, why do people like them, who want to
save the world like the burly center, want to save the girlfriend, and
why do they enjoy the film,
they want to be superheroes in a hall of
us, in our lives, when we
have a moment, their teeth, are twelve years
old,
we ask ourselves a question, ask
ourselves, why am I, why did I
come here, why
Am I in this world? Why was
I born here where I was born?
What is my life? 17 years and
we feel hungry. Jadwiga, there are
three great forms of hunger in
man.
[Music]
We like the first one, all people love it,
only on the 26th.
We all like six trainers. I have in the
Rhine Halls. Fortune has only in
billions, and men, half a million
women are looking for three and a half billion men.
Three and a half billion
men are looking for three and a half million
women.
That is the world in which always with that
the two great desires of man,
there is a third desire.
I want to save this world. He understands,
I want to help every person because they are
stricter, stronger than the desire for,
and stronger is the desire for,
and everyone has that, but we
all have that. If you learn the pen,
if the used to be successful,
because then you can be better than
Biden,
you will become Transformer Number Four.
That is because you are different, because of the
bag - accessories. That is the second
meaning of super. The first meaning
is the guys who don't understand the pen.
I play with
rich, rich Mr. Young, whether  They do
n't understand the pen and they will get
older and eventually die and
that counts as losing. The
second superhero is Penn, the
pen's superhero.
They are successful and happy.
They know how to
reinvest their money and understand
how to help others.
That's what I mean when you say that's the pen's
superhero.
That's supposed to be the pen's superhero.
It shouldn't be the other superhero who is
very powerful. Then, of
course, it's true, but two
different superheroes. Stay with
me,
we have to continue.
After 20 minutes, my teacher said
a day corresponds to... She would have had a
car accident.
She's especially the stars in New York. I
know that girls serve and now it's been a
long time since... probably by train... the room
is... so you can... is the room too
hot? Now go to the toilet.
I understand that. Then she... but it's
completely irrelevant to me. How do
you have 20 minutes at the moment?
A teacher was a tough guy.
The problem is the train.
I have... The spirit was born here.
With Ducati, we have the body and...
Spirit assumed
Julia Baun July because when you are born, it is always like
an airplane
landed at an airport and the radiometer,
you get a mediator this
year, and this one here in the
global, the one you find, you are born, you get
a body, your spirit, because
right in this body there is a problem
and the body can't, that the air
conditioning is on and off, the door to the
beach, out and can go back to the
beach in Thailand from the vacation, and
then you come home, when you
live at home,
it forces you to move, to move, to move,
I can't do much about that,
and the spirit is exactly the same, it works similarly,
I have now applied for a job,
applied at a great
company, Havana, the biggest accounting company,
I hope I get the job because if it ever
goes well, then you get the job, I have
the job, let go out to eat and
celebrate,
six weeks later the chance, this
job has, yes, work is forbidden,
the boss is never satisfied, nature is
born, I have met a new guy, it's
okay, he is like that, really likes me a lot,
six weeks later, a holds,
I hate him, yes, as every  Another person
in the world,
I hate it's not the person, it
's not the worker, the
workplace, it's our own mind
that you pack, you got the rental car,
they gave you a broken meter, every
[music]
this part and this part is defective,
you can't be happy in this body and this
mind, that's
impossible, wanting to go out into the sun,
you'll always want to go back from
the sun, and you're always going to want to meet a bitter, evil one,
and
then you'll, is that boring where I
say it has nothing to do with the guy,
I'll tell you an interesting
experiment you can try,
room, yesterday, a room with ten
people, guest, go into the room with ten
other people, after an hour, up to
three of them will,
we don't want to, are rather
indifferent, 334, now as always, the
three you paint, seven others to that
you also make, bring them into a
second room, bring the hour
with them, after an hour, three of
them like,
three of them don't like, and
four of them will be equally indifferent, are
not the people and I around, that's
you in  The mind is 30 30 40, the
mind from the factory is set up like that,
even a donkey.
Pauli has taken on a body
in the pizza pudding, and people
give things to hit the donkey
because it is, and that is the nature of their
body. Dollar Cad to Banana Bay to the
national tumor, their fans, Judas.
Once you've taken on a body,
something happens to the body, even just
the sun on a rose, Byrne on a
big opera, a little pain all day,
only you come to realize that's not a
problem of the world. Body problems
are a problem of your body.
You have a wrong body, this
body is impossible to make happy. You can't make
this mind a wrong body.
We got into the wrong body,
difficult to get out of.
Not if you take one against nails,
they call it, said the media, on the
back of the link, clicks, then it
hurts. Some of them will, until he
gives this bag down, does it hurt if
you were born in a body like this one?
Things we will do
until the time you die, we
have to put this body in
Take off the shirt,
we have to take off this body,
you can do that, it's possible, then
you can get a new model, a
good new model, or Daddy, a
Buddha body. Brother Klaus,
my Christians,
visited me at the monastery. I took him with me to
show him in the temple because he's so beautiful.
Then he looked at everything. When
we left the temple,
he said, "I don't understand
why the policeman...
what's wrong? Who wants to look like that?"
He says what's wrong, and what's wrong
with the police? They have this big bang on their heads
from their long ears.
It doesn't look so good. I don't want to
understand why. I don't understand why you are. I have to
understand.
Sometimes I tell myself, the students of the
girl, if it's a girl, I say, "
I bought the Vogue magazine, I want to
see the most beautiful woman from Seesen." You can see that's you.
If you go to Budapest, the
boys have to buy the heartfelt Kyu
magazine, which I find beautiful and fractures.
You can choose if you are. You, the
show, is the body you
can imagine.
Unimaginable seemed and  Immortal and
never again take it with you to go to the toilet.
I had an incredible amount of time, where to go, don't know anymore, don't
shave,
I think that, I don't want the head,
I don't want a big fat belly like my
brother, that's
not how it is, you will be the most
elegant and exquisite thing you
can imagine, pain-free, you ca
n't have pain,
we have to prevent the body, even if you
do yoga or eat right food,
the body is still and still
a problem, getting
older and older,
he won't get cancer anymore, people
say don't worry, when
you die, a special prayer, at that
time, guests, then to a Buddha
body, it is possible to make a person out of
a billion dollars, it is
possible to make a person out of a billion, you can
wait
until the last minute and then
get your brother's body, but it is very
dangerous,
99 percent fail, take care of it
now,
you have to, for two days, three days,
you go from the plate to home and bank
today.de and enjoy that for two days, do
n't have to think about it, think now about
the  They tried to get budak, but now do
n't wait for the last day of
your life, you'll probably
fail. Change your body now,
learn how to change the body,
and little one, it's now.
We reject the inhabitation of the diamond. The
body is a living diamond. How to
get this body, there's
a special gathering for it. What is
the gathering? It empties directly, very
empty. It has right at the moment when you
get cancer and your friend has cancer, she
's sad. That's a beautiful
person. In the episode, she gets breast cancer
because she started to grow,
collapses,
then gets bigger and bigger, much too
uncontrolled growth, and the body
of them.
That's how you keep one. Today I had a
banana in Sochi. It looked good from outside,
the sun hadn't been on it yet. A treasure of
theirs would have been pursued. That's what
makes cancer. Skin is here, the skin is
still there, but inside, tortured body.
Sadly, you can't stop it.
No one emphasizes slowing it down,
but not stopping it.
If you're direct, it's the opposite.
A cell becomes a life, the diamond.
The two numbers become the teaching
diamond in the conflict, one, three.  Cells
become living diamonds. At the point when you're
empty, you see directly that
the body starts cancer again, beginning
from the inside out. It doesn't change, and
the body begins to resist.
Then it can't be stopped. There is
no cure. The body, the
first cell, begins immortal and approximately
pain-free, and your family can also
learn from you. If you teach directly,
it starts the process of change, which
is unstoppable.
When you're empty, you understand. In Mexico, this
changes the inside.
You can no longer go to hell. You
can no longer.
We will. Something changes within you,
and for this reason, teachers become foundations,
and again and again. As
he clearly stated, we have a
children's class. What is the best thing your
mother did for you?
They all say different
things. Then, as I said, what is the best thing
you did for your mother?
I truly believe that, by the way, the
children understand these four steps very well,
and I believe their parents are doing
a good job.
[Applause]
I taught children for 15 years.
It was a globalization. He
says I have a  Abortion, he did that
in college, although in his own box. I
wasn't a police officer at the time.
I didn't understand what I was doing. Did
I tell my teacher?
When I was younger, an
abortion...
You have to clean the sperm.
How can I clean it? I said, "I
think you destroyed it." Therefore,
you should teach children. Children,
children, behind the teacher, and clearly
stated how long the sperm lasts.
You want to know.
Your heart will open. Friend
found
a heart completely different. They fell until
then. The heart will weigh heavily. 5. I did
n't understand. I
checked my heart and I
realized he was right. I'm a little
sad. Is there something I should
do?
Maybe he'll bring... Children at the
same time started with the... with the
parents of the children, with the parents of the
children, with their permission,
and they also come to the class. With
them, I brought the donors. They
taught the four steps. There's
a nice story. One
day in summer, very, very hot. Jörg is
usually quite good and pleasant.
Better ocean, but...  In summer it's
very unpleasantly
humid and we use air conditioning.
I've been in this child's
class for 15 years before I felt there was
a change.
When it's daytime, the air conditioning is
broken and I wanted to try to
fix it. Then one of the
children
pulled my pants. Later, their parade... the
air conditioning...
he always pulled my pants.
I have to fix the air conditioning.
These titles explain what's going on. What do you
want? Fix the air conditioning.
It's so hot. I'm fixing the air conditioning.
That's not the way you
fix the air conditioning. What's the
right way? Go out... Another
person... the annoyance... just... They
have a problem with the air conditioning.
You hold the air conditioning and fix
the air conditioning. The others... that gesture...
then we would
n't have the air conditioning today. Hood in hand...
OK... Mandala
[Music]
Senate...
they aren't...
[Music]
No,
thank you...
Cham...
Yes
[Music]
So beautiful
June...
OK